cure.fit 2019-12-06

# None

We at Diverse Retails Private Limited ('CureFit', 'We', 'Us', 'Our') know that you as a user ('You', 'Your', ‘User(s)’) care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting or using our website (www.cure.fit) and domain name, and any other linked pages, features, content, mobile applications, or any other services we offer from time to time by in connection therewith (collectively, the 'Mobile App'), or by using the Services / Products (as defined in our  [Terms of Use](https://static.cure.fit/terms.html) ) in any manner, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this privacy policy, and you hereby consent that we will collect, use, and share your information in the following ways. 

If you reside in or use / access the Mobile App in United Arab Emirates, Privacy Policy for UAE region, as published immediately below this privacy policy, shall apply. 

What does this privacy policy cover? 

This privacy policy covers our treatment of personally identifiable information ('personal information') that we gather when you are accessing or using our Mobile App and Products. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that we do not own or control, or to individuals that we do not employ or manage.

We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 18 or knowingly allow such persons to register for the Products. If you are under 18, please do not attempt to register for the Products or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, email address or provide your biometric information. No one under age 18 may provide any personal information to us or on the Products. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 18 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 18, please contact us at  [hello@cure.fit](mailto:hello@cure.fit) .

What information does CureFit collect?

We gather various types of personal information from our users, as explained more fully below. We may use this personal information to personalize and improve our services, to allow our users to set up a user account and profile, to contact users, to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, to analyze how users utilize the Mobile App and Product, and as otherwise set forth in this privacy policy. We may share certain types of personal information with third parties. We collect the following types of information: 

Information you provide to us:

We receive and store any information you knowingly provide to us. For example, we collect personal information such as your name, username, email address, gender, birth date, weight, height, location, nutrition data, workouts, physical activity, photographs, biometric information, and sleep habits and we may collect other sleep, activity, or health-related information as our services and products are further developed. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to register with us or to take advantage of some of our features / Products. We may anonymize your personal information so that you cannot be individually identified, and provide that information to our partners. For example, you may tell us that you are female and sleep an average of 6 hours per night; we may combine this information with content received from our other users, and disclose to our partners that on the whole, our male users sleep more hours per night than our female ones, but we will not tell those partners who you are.

Information collected automatically:

Whenever you interact with our Mobile App, we automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, 'cookie' information, and the page you requested. 'Cookies' are identifiers we transfer to your computer or mobile device that allow us to recognize your browser or mobile device and tell us how and when pages in our Mobile App are visited and by how many people. You may be able to change the preferences on your browser or mobile device to prevent or limit your computer or device's acceptance of cookies, but this may prevent you from taking advantage of our Mobile App's best features. 

When we collect usage information (such as the numbers and frequency of visitors to the Mobile App), we only use this data in aggregate form, and not in a manner that would identify you personally. For example, this aggregate data tells us how often users use parts of the Mobile App, so that we can make the Mobile App appealing to as many users as possible. We may also provide this aggregate information to our partners; our partners may use such information to understand how often people use our Mobile App, so that they, too, can provide you with an optimal online experience. We never disclose aggregate information to a partner in a manner that would identify you personally. 

If you are using our Products, you understand and acknowledge that, any information, data or readings from the Product, or collected from Your use thereof, will be automatically uploaded to your account with us. To the extent these automatically collected readings can be used to personally identify you, these readings are personal information for the purposes of this privacy policy. 

Delete targeting cookies

Your interest profile can be removed by deleting your browser's cookies.

Information stored on cookies

The cookie information stored on the User's hard drive is: (i) User segment hits or information on a specific product, service, brand or model in which the User has shown interest during its visit to a certain website and (ii) time and date stamp of the latest update of the User profile. 

If the cookie is deleted by the User, all profile data is removed. For the sake of clarity, no segments relating to information which CureFit considers sensitive have been or will be created, such as segments relating to political opinions, religious beliefs, physical or mental health conditions or sexual life. Further, CureFit is very sensitive to the issue of children's privacy and marketing directed to children. No segments are intended to be established for the profiling of children. 

E-mail and other communications:

We may contact you, by email or other means; for example, we may send you promotional offers on behalf of other businesses, or communicate with you about your use of the Mobile App or the Product. Also, we may receive a confirmation when you open an email from us. This confirmation helps us make emails more interesting and improve our service. If you do not want to receive email or other mail from us, please indicate your preference by emailing us at  [hello@cure.fit](mailto:hello@cure.fit) .

Will CureFit share any of the personal information it receives?

We neither rent nor sell your personal information in personally identifiable form to anyone. We share your personal information in personally identifiable form with third parties only as described below. In terms of the Diverse Services, the Company shall share the information collected from You with only such third parties in relation to whom you provide express consent. 

  * Affiliated businesses and third-party websites we do not control:   In certain situations, businesses or third party websites we're affiliated with may sell items or provide services to you through the Mobile App (either alone or jointly with us). You can recognize when an affiliated business is associated with such a transaction or service, and we will share your personal information with that affiliated business only to the extent that it is related to such transaction or service.
  * Agents:  We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide Products or services to you. Unless we tell you differently, our agents do not have any right to use the personal information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us. 
  * User submissions:  Any content or personal information that you voluntarily disclose online in a manner other users can view (on discussion boards, in messages and chat areas, etc.) becomes publicly available, and can be collected and used by others.
  * Business transfers:   We may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Also, if we (or substantially all of our assets) are acquired, or if we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, personal information would be one of the assets transferred to or acquired by a third party.
  * Protection of CureFit and others:   We may release personal information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with laws; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Curefit, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
  * With your consent:   Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your personal information may be shared with third parties, and will be able to prevent the sharing of this information.

Is personal information about me secure?

Your account is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You need to prevent unauthorized access to your account and personal information by selecting and protecting your password appropriately and limiting access to your computer or device and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your account. 

We endeavor to protect the privacy of your account and other personal information we hold in our records, but we cannot guarantee complete security. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time. 

Mobile App may contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When following a link to another site you should read that site's privacy policy. 

Note:  However, as effective as encryption technology is, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information you supply won't be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet. Any transmission of information by you to our Mobile App or otherwise is at your own risk. 

What personal information can I access?

Through your account settings, you may access, and, in some cases, edit or delete the following information you've provided to us: 

  * name and password
  * email address
  * user profile information, including your height, weight, and location

The information you can view and update may change as the Mobile App changes. Please note that any information that is automatically uploaded from a Product to the Mobile App, or collected otherwise from You by us, cannot be later changed or updated. If you have any questions about viewing or updating information we have on file about you, please contact us at:  [hello@cure.fit](mailto:hello@cure.fit) .

What choices do I have?

You can always opt not to disclose information to use, but keep in mind some information may be needed to register with us or to take advantage of some of our special features / Products. We will retain Your personal information for a reasonable period or as long as the law requires. If you’d like us to delete/modify Information that you have provided via the Mobile App or otherwise to us, please contact us at  [hello@cure.fit](mailto:hello@cure.fit)  and we will respond in a reasonable time. Please note that some or all of the Information provided by You to us may be required in order for the Mobile App / Products to function properly. 

You may be able to add, update, or delete information as explained in section above. When you update information, however, we may maintain a copy of the unrevised information in our records. Please note that some information may remain in our private records after your deletion of such information from your account. We may use any aggregated data derived from or incorporating your personal information after you update or delete it, but not in a manner that would identify you personally. 

If you do not wish to receive email or other mail from us, please email us at:  [hello@cure.fit](mailto:hello@cure.fit) . Please note that if you do not want to receive legal notices from us, such as this privacy policy, those legal notices will still govern your use of the Mobile App and the Product, and you are responsible for reviewing such legal notices for changes. 

Changes to this privacy policy

We may amend this privacy policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the privacy policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes in the way we use personal information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our Mobile App or sending you an email. You are bound by any changes to the privacy policy when you use the Mobile App or the Product after such changes have been first posted. 

How is my iOS HealthKit, Health app and Google Fit data handled?

When you share your iOS Health app data or Google Fit with our Products, that data is covered by the privacy policy. 

We handle all iOS Health app and HealthKit data in accordance with Apple's development guidelines. To view Apple's HealthKit developer guidelines, go to  [ https://developer.apple.com/app-store/review/guidelines/#health-and-health-research](https://developer.apple.com/app-store/review/guidelines/#health-and-health-research) .

We handle Google Fit data in accordance with Google Fit Terms of Service. To view Google Fit Terms of Service go to  [ https://developers.google.com/fit/terms](https://developers.google.com/fit/terms) .

HealthKit, Health app, iPhone, and Apple are registered trademarks of Apple Inc. 

Google Fit and Google are registered trademark of Google Inc. 

PRIVACY POLICY (for United Arab Emirates region)

We at CureFit Fitness LLC ('Company', ‘CureFit’, 'We', 'Us,' 'Our') know that you as a user ('You,' 'Your', ‘User(s)’) care about how your personal information is collected, used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting or using our mobile application, and related website and m-web, or any other services we offer from time to time by in connection therewith (collectively, the 'Platform'), or by using the Service(s) (as defined in our   [Terms of Use](https://static.cure.fit/terms.html) ) in any manner, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this privacy policy, and you hereby consent that we will collect, use, and share your information in the following ways. 

What does this privacy policy cover? 

This privacy policy covers our treatment of personally identifiable information ('personal information') that we gather when you are accessing or using our Platform and Services. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that we do not own or control, or to individuals that we do not employ or manage.

We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of majority or knowingly allow such persons to register for the Services. If you are under the age of majority, please do not attempt to register for the Services or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, email address or provide your biometric information. No one under age of majority may provide any personal information to us or on the Services. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from an individual under the age of majority without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under the age of majority, please contact us at  [hello@cure.fit](mailto:hello@cure.fit) . 

What information does CureFit collect?

We gather various types of personal information from our users, as explained more fully below. We may use this personal information to personalize and improve our services, to allow our users to set up a user account and profile, to contact users, to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, to analyze how users utilize the Platform and Services / Products, and as otherwise set forth in this privacy policy. We may share certain types of personal information with third parties. We collect the following types of information: 

Information you provide to us:

We receive and store any information you knowingly provide to us. For example, we collect personal information such as your name, username, email address, gender, birth date, weight, height, location, nutrition data, workouts, physical activity, photographs, biometric information, and sleep habits and we may collect other sleep, activity, or health-related information as our services and products are further developed. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to register with us or to take advantage of some of our features / Services / Products. We may anonymize your personal information so that you cannot be individually identified, and provide that information to our partners. For example, you may tell us that you are female and sleep an average of 6 hours per night; we may combine this information with content received from our other users, and disclose to our partners that on the whole, our male users sleep more hours per night than our female ones, but we will not tell those partners who you are.

Information collected automatically:

Whenever you interact with our Platform, we automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, 'cookie' information, device information and the page you requested. 'Cookies' are identifiers we transfer to your computer or mobile device that allow us to recognize your browser or mobile device and tell us how and when pages in our Platform are visited and by how many people. You may be able to change the preferences on your browser or mobile device to prevent or limit your computer or device's acceptance of cookies, but this may prevent you from taking advantage of our Platform's best features. 

When we collect usage information (such as the numbers and frequency of visitors to the Platform), we only use this data in aggregate form, and not in a manner that would identify you personally. For example, this aggregate data tells us how often users use parts of the Platform, so that we can make the Platform appealing to as many users as possible. We may also provide this aggregate information to our partners; our partners may use such information to understand how often people use our Platform, so that they, too, can provide you with an optimal online experience. We never disclose aggregate information to a partner in a manner that would identify you personally. 

If you are using our Services / Products, you understand and acknowledge that, any information, data or readings from the Services / Products, or collected from Your use thereof, will be automatically uploaded to your account with us. To the extent these automatically collected readings can be used to personally identify you, these readings are personal information for the purposes of this privacy policy. 

Delete targeting cookies

Your interest profile can be removed by deleting your browser's cookies.

Information stored on cookies

The cookie information stored on the User's hard drive is: (i) User segment hits or information on a specific Service / Product, service, brand or model in which the User has shown interest during its visit to a certain website and (ii) time and date stamp of the latest update of the User profile. 

If the cookie is deleted by the User, all profile data is removed. For the sake of clarity, no segments relating to information which Company considers sensitive have been or will be created, such as segments relating to political opinions, religious beliefs, physical or mental health conditions or sexual life. Further, we are very sensitive to the issue of children's privacy and marketing directed to children. No segments are intended to be established for the profiling of children. 

E-mail and other communications:

We may contact you, by email or other means; for example, we may send you promotional offers on behalf of other businesses, or communicate with you about your use of the Platform or the Services / Products. Also, we may receive a confirmation when you open an email from us. This confirmation helps us make emails more interesting and improve our service. If you do not want to receive email or other mail from us, please indicate your preference by emailing us at  [hello@cure.fit](mailto:hello@cure.fit) .

Will Company share any of the personal information it receives?

We neither rent nor sell your personal information in personally identifiable form to anyone. We share your personal information in personally identifiable form with third parties only as described below 

  * Affiliated businesses and third-party websites we do not control:    In certain situations, businesses or third-party websites we're affiliated with, may sell items or provide services to you through the Platform (either alone or jointly with us). You can recognize when an affiliated business is associated with such a transaction or service, and we will share your personal information with that affiliated business only to the extent that it is related to such transaction or service.
  * Agents:  We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide Services or Products to you. Unless we tell you differently, our agents do not have any right to use the personal information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us. 
  * User submissions:  Any content or personal information that you voluntarily disclose online in a manner other users can view (on discussion boards, in messages and chat areas, etc.) becomes publicly available, and can be collected and used by others.
  * Business transfers:   We may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Also, if we (or substantially all of our assets) are acquired, or if we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, personal information would be one of the assets transferred to or acquired by a third party.
  * Protection of CureFit and others:    We may release personal information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with laws; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Company, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
  * With your consent:    Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your personal information may be shared with third parties, and will be able to prevent the sharing of this information.

Is personal information about me secure?

Your account is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You need to prevent unauthorized access to your account and personal information by selecting and protecting your password appropriately and limiting access to your computer or device and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your account. 

We endeavor to protect the privacy of your account and other personal information we hold in our records, but we cannot guarantee complete security. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time. 

Platform may contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When following a link to another site you should read that site's privacy policy. 

Note:  However, as effective as encryption technology is, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information you supply won't be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet. Any transmission of information by you to our Platform or otherwise is at your own risk. 

What personal information can I access?

Through your account settings, you may access, and, in some cases, edit or delete the following information you've provided to us: 

  * name and password
  * email address
  * user profile information, including your height, weight, and location

The information you can view and update may change as the Platform changes. Please note that any information that is automatically uploaded from a Service / Product to the Platform, or collected otherwise from You by us, cannot be later changed or updated. If you have any questions about viewing or updating information we have on file about you, please contact us at:  [hello@cure.fit](mailto:hello@cure.fit) .

What choices do I have?

You can always opt not to disclose information to use, but keep in mind some information may be needed to register with us or to take advantage of some of our special features / Services / Products. We will retain Your personal information for a reasonable period or as long as the law requires. If you’d like us to delete/modify Information that you have provided via the Platform or otherwise to us, please contact us at  [hello@cure.fit](mailto:hello@cure.fit)  and we will respond in a reasonable time. Please note that some or all of the Information provided by You to us may be required in order for the Platform / Services to function properly. 

You may be able to add, update, or delete information as explained in section above. When you update information, however, we may maintain a copy of the unrevised information in our records. Please note that some information may remain in our private records after your deletion of such information from your account. We may use any aggregated data derived from or incorporating your personal information after you update or delete it, but not in a manner that would identify you personally. 

If you do not wish to receive email or other mail from us, please email us at:  [hello@cure.fit](mailto:hello@cure.fit) . Please note that if you do not want to receive legal notices from us, such as this privacy policy, those legal notices will still govern your use of the Platform and the Service / Product, and you are responsible for reviewing such legal notices for changes. 

Changes to this privacy policy

We may amend this privacy policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the privacy policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes in the way we use personal information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our Platform or sending you an email. You are bound by any changes to the privacy policy when you use the Platform or the Services / Products after such changes have been first posted. 

How is my iOS HealthKit, Health app and Google Fit data handled?

When you share your iOS Health app data or Google Fit with our Products, that data is covered by the privacy policy. 

We handle all iOS Health app and HealthKit data in accordance with Apple's development guidelines. To view Apple's HealthKit developer guidelines, go to  [ https://developer.apple.com/app-store/review/guidelines/#health-and-health-research](https://developer.apple.com/app-store/review/guidelines/#health-and-health-research) .

We handle Google Fit data in accordance with Google Fit Terms of Service. To view Google Fit Terms of Service go to  [ https://developers.google.com/fit/terms](https://developers.google.com/fit/terms) .

HealthKit, Health app, iPhone, and Apple are registered trademarks of Apple Inc. 

Google Fit and Google are registered trademark of Google Inc. 

Last Updated on 13 May 2019.

Copyright © All rights reserved.
